ledful.com 2019-06-12

# Privacy Policy - 2008-2018 LEDFUL

Welcome to LEDFUL's Privacy Policy

**Privacy principles** : Our privacy principles will protect users and visitors any private information from third-party.

Your privacy is important to us. This Privacy Policy explains what data LEDFUL collects from you through our interactions and through our products, why we collect it, and what we do with it. We hope you will take time to read it carefully.

**Personal Data we collect**

LEDFUL collects data to operate effectively and provide you the best experiences with our products– from figuring out basic stuff like which language you speak, to more complex things like which products you will find most useful, how many square meters of LED display you need and what kind of pixel pitch is suitable for your application.

**How we use Personal Data we collect**

LEDFUL uses data to operate our business, improve our products and personalize your experiences. However, we do not use what you say in email, chat, video calls or voice mail, or your documents, photos or other personal files to target ads to you

**Personal Data we share**

LEDFUL do not share personal data with other companies, organizations and individuals unless one of the following circumstances applies:

With your consent

LEDFUL will share personal data with companies, organizations or individuals outside of LEDFUL when we have your consent. We require opt-in consent for the sharing of any sensitive personal information.

For external processing

LEDFUL provides personal data to our affiliates or other trusted businesses or persons to process it for us, based on our instructions and in compliance with our Privacy Policy and any other appropriate confidentiality and security measures.

For legal reasons

LEDFUL will share personal data with companies, organizations or individuals outside of LEDFUL if we have a good-faith belief that access, use, preservation or disclosure of the information is reasonably necessary to:  
1）meet any applicable law, regulation, legal process or enforceable governmental request.

2）enforce applicable Terms of Service, including investigation of potential violations.

3）detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues.

4）protect against harm to the right, property or safety of LEDFUL, our users or the public as required or permitted by law.

LEDFUL may share non-personally identifiable information publicly and with our partners – like publishers, advertisers or connected sites. For example, LEDFUL may share data publicly to show trends about our products.

If LEDFUL is involved in a merger, acquisition or asset sale, we will continue to ensure the confidentiality of any personal information and give affected users notice before personal information is transferred or becomes subject to a different private policy.
